# RASMUS LADEFOGED CARLSEN Software Engineer



## **CONTACTS**

Phone: +45 71907535

Email: rasmus.lc3@gmail.com

#### LINKS

#### Portfolio:

https://rasmuslc1.github.io/portfolio\_website/

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/rcarlsen853/

Github:

https://github.com/RasmusLC1

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: C/C++, Python, JavaScript, TypeScript, C#, CSS

Frameworks/Libraries: React, Next.js,Node.NET, Numpy,

Tools/Technologies: Git, Node.js, Azure, PostgreSQL, JSON

# **PROJECTS**

- Dungeon Crawler Game
  (Python): Designed and
  developed a game using Object Oriented Programming (OOP)
  principles and efficient
  algorithms to dynamically
  generate engaging gameplay.
- Fullstack Recipe App (React, TypeScript): Designed a Recipe app with support for dynamically created recipes, local storage, and image integration.
- Bachelor Project (C): Focused on efficient algorithmic implementation and testing

# **PROFILE**

Computer Science graduate specialising in problem solving and efficient implementation. My experience in System Administration and IT Support has provided me with a solid understanding of IT infrastructure.

Recently, I have been working on various hobby projects, which have refined my creativity, discipline, and focus. These projects have outlined the importance of maintainability and a structured approach to development.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### LanguageWire, Copenhagen - IT Student Assistant March 2023 - September 2024

- Managed Azure and Active Directory databases. Assisted with the implementation and testing of Mobile Device Management using Autopilot.
- Created and maintained an organised inventory database to track stock levels and procure equipment to reduce downtime for staff.

### **Apple, Cork - Specialist Product Support**

May 2020 - September 2020 (COVID-19)

- Completed Apple Level 3 training for enterprise networking support and Mobile Device Management solutions.
- Managed server and business account administration, providing remote support for enterprise-level hardware and software issues.

#### Accenture, Dublin - QA Testing for Google

December 2017 - August 2018

 Developed automated bug reporting and testing solutions to streamline workflows, enhance productivity, and improve consistency

## Concentrix, Belfast - Social Media Representative for Microsoft November 2016 - September 2017

 Optimized workflows for Windows, Office, and Microsoft Account support, enhancing KPIs and SLA performance for the Danish market

# **EDUCATION**

#### Bachelor in Computer Science, Copenhagen University September 2021 - November 2024

Focus on low level implementation, IT security and algorithms